<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android by Roger</string>

    <!--    STRINGS FOR THE MAIN APPLICATION-->
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="details_activity">Details</string>
    <string name="action_settings">About</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="card">Business Card</string>
    <string name="scorekeeper">Scorekeeper</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz App</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="guide">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="news">Guardian APIs</string>
    <string name="cat">Category</string>
    <string name="news_img_desc">News</string>
    <string name="news_id">News</string>
    <string name="news_desc">News Description</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="credentials">Credentials</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Program Syllabus"\n

"This program is divided into 5 parts and 6 projects you need to complete in order to receive your certificate."\n\n

PART 1: Welcome to the Nanodegree\n
An introduction to your Nanodegree program.\n\n

PART 2: User Interface\n
Learn how to transform your hand-drawn app designs into layouts using the XML markup language, and use Views and ViewGroups — the building blocks of an Android app\'s user interface — to display images and text.\n\n

        Project 1: Build a Single Screen App\n\n

PART 3: User Input\n
Harness the power of Java to build a coffee-ordering app, use variables to add interactivity to your app, and learn the basics of object-oriented programming.\n\n

        Project 2: Score Keeper App\n

        Project 3: Quiz App\n\n

PART 4: Multi-Screen Apps\n
Learn how to show multiple screens in a Miwok language app, and add audio and images to your app. You\'ll also learn how Android handles touch events, and make visual changes to add polish to your fully functional app.\n\n

        Project 4: Musical Structure App\n

        Project 5: Tour Guide App\n\n

PART 5: Networking"\n
Discover the power of Web APIs and how to use them in your apps, and learn the basics of networking in Android, including HTTP networking, JSON parsing, and threads.\n\n

        Project 6: News App\n
    </string>

    <!--    Java Projects-->
    <string name="java_one_name">Single Screen App</string>
    <string name="java_one_details">Design and implement a single screen app that displays information about a small business that you are closely familiar with.</string>
    <string name="java_one_description">PROJECT SPECIFICATION\n
Build a Single Screen App\n\n

Your design must include:\n

Business name\n
At least one photo representing the business\n
Two or more other pieces of information, such as:\n
Contact information for the business (eg phone number, email address, website)\n
Address of the Business\n
Description of business\n
Hours of operation\n
Functionality\n\n

MEETS SPECIFICATIONS\n\n
Program compiles and runs on a phone\n

Program must function in Android Studio emulator and on a phone. Upon launching on a phone, the card appears.\n

Content does not appear "cut off"\n

Layout scales responsively for screen sizes in portrait mode, with no part of any images only partially visible. Student is not responsible for responsive design in landscape mode.\n

Note: Reviewers will test on a Nexus 5X which has a screen size of 5.2 inches (132.08mm). It is advised you test on this size at minimum. If your content does not fit on this size, consider implementing a ScrollView.\n

At least one View Group is included\n

XML must include a Relative Layout, Linear Layout, or Constraint Layout\n

View Groups contain at least one image view and at least one text view\n

Must have one or more image views or text views.\n

Elements and Text on screen are in appropriate units\n

Elements are specified in dp, text is specified in sp.</string>
    <string name="java_one_location">Passed on: Thu, Nov 7 2:20 pm</string>

    <string name="java_two_name">User Input</string>
    <string name="java_two_details">Design and implement an app to track scores between two teams playing a game.</string>
    <string name="java_two_description">PROJECT SPECIFICATION\n
Score Keeper\n\n

The chosen game has either multiple amounts of points that can be scored, as in american football, or multiple important metrics to track, such as fouls, outs, and innings in baseball.\n\n

Overall layout\n

App is divided into two columns, one for each team.\n\n

Column contents\n

Each column contains a large TextView to keep track of the current score for that team.\n

Optionally, a second TextView to track another important metric such as fouls can be added.\n

Score buttons\n\n

Each column contains multiple buttons. The buttons must track either:\n

Each track a different kind of scoring\n

Or\n

Each track a different metric (one score, the other fouls, for instance).\n\n

Reset button\n

The layout contains a ‘reset’ button.\n\n

Best practices\n\n

The code adheres to all of the following best practices:\n

Text sizes are defined in sp\n
Lengths are defined in dp\n
Padding and margin is used appropriately, such that the views are not crammed up against each other.\n\n
Functionality\n\n

MEETS SPECIFICATIONS\n
The code runs without errors.\n\n

Score Button Function\n

Each score button updates the score TextView in its column by adding the correct number of points.\n\n

Reset Button Function\n

The reset button resets the scores on both of the score TextViews.\n\n

Code Readability\n\n

Naming conventions\n

Any classes are named after the object they represent.All variables are named by their intended contents.\n

All methods are named by their intended effect or in the style required by a callback interface.\n\n

Code style\n

There are no unnecessary blank lines.One variable is declared per declaration line.\n

The code within a method is indented with respect to the method declaration line.</string>
    <string name="java_two_location">Passed on: Thu, Nov 14 11:05 pm</string>

    <string name="java_three_name">User Input</string>
    <string name="java_three_details">Design and implement a short quiz app about some topic you are familiar with.</string>
    <string name="java_three_description">TODO</string>
    <string name="java_three_location">Passed on: Thu, Dec 5 6:12 am</string>

    <string name="java_four_name">Musical Structure</string>
    <string name="java_four_details">Multi Screen</string>
    <string name="java_four_description">TODO</string>
    <string name="java_four_location">Project 4</string>

    <string name="java_five_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="java_five_details">Multi Screen</string>
    <string name="java_five_description">TODO</string>
    <string name="java_five_location">Project 5</string>

    <string name="java_six_name">News API</string>
    <string name="java_six_details">Networking</string>
    <string name="java_six_description">TODO</string>
    <string name="java_six_location">Project 6</string>

    <!--    Images' descriptions-->
    <string name="image_description">cape_image</string>
    <string name="image_background_description">Background for opaque image</string>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="phone_contact">Phone Contact</string>
    <string name="mail_contact">Email Contact</string>

    <!--    Drawings' Strings-->
    <string name="drawing_one_name">Sketch 1</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_details">Sketch 1 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_description">Sketch 1 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_location">Sketch 1 location</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_name">Sketch 2</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_details">Sketch 2 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_description">Sketch 2 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_location">Sketch 2 location</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_name">Sketch 3</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_details">Sketch 3 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_description">Sketch 3 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_location">Sketch 3 location</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_name">Sketch 4</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_details">Sketch 4 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_description">Sketch 4 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_location">Sketch 4 location</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Welcome to my Android Portfolio.\n\nClicking on a project will display its details\n\nLong clicking a project will open the selected app for testing.</string>
    <string name="action_intro">Introduction</string>
    <string name="telNum">27789871987</string>
    <string name="emailAddress">roger.vanwyk@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>

</resources>