<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Android by Roger</string>

    <!--    STRINGS FOR THE MAIN APPLICATION-->
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="details_activity">Details</string>
    <string name="action_settings">About</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="card">Business Card</string>
    <string name="scorekeeper">Scorekeeper</string>
    <string name="quiz">Quiz App</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="guide">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="news">Guardian APIs</string>
    <string name="cat">Category</string>
    <string name="news_img_desc">News</string>
    <string name="news_id">News</string>
    <string name="news_desc">News Description</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="credentials">Credentials</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>
    <string name="demo_title">Demo Title</string>
    <string name="demo_content">Demo description</string>
    <string name="onboarding_content_one">Develop</string>
    <string name="onboarding_sub_content_one">Projects written in Java &amp; Kotlin programming languages.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_content_two">Design</string>
    <string name="onboarding_sub_content_two">From mock-ups, logos, to your app, following Android\'s
    Material Design Concepts.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_content_three">Communicate</string>
    <string name="onboarding_sub_content_three">Get in touch with a call, an email, or a virtual meeting.
    All this is possible at the click of a button.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_content_four">Share</string>
    <string name="onboarding_sub_content_four">Share this app, or download and share my CV.</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Roger van Wyk"\n

"Android Everywhere developer"\n\n

Java Android Basics NanoDegree (ASSESSED)\n
Google grant to learn basic Android app development through www.udacity.com\n\n

Kotlin Android Basics NanoDegree (UN-ASSESSED)\n
Free learning at www.udacity.com\n\n

Java Android Advanced Development\n
www.udacity.com AND other platforms eg. www.developers_android.com, www.stack-overflow.com,
        www.medium.com, etc. etc.\n\n

Kotlin Android Advanced Development\n
In progress; To be completed shortly.\n\n

Proficient\n
Adobe Illustrator\n\n
        Adobe Photoshop\n\n
        AutoDesk Sketchbook Pro\n\n
        Android Studio\n\n
        IntelliJ IDEA\n\n

    </string>

    <!--    Java Projects-->
    <string name="java_one_name">Card</string>
    <string name="java_one_description">Design and implement a single screen app that displays information about a fictional small business.
        Think along the lines of your favorite coffeeshop, local restaurant, or that gem of a store that sells those rare comic books or records.</string>
    <string name="java_one_category">User Interface</string>
    <string name="java_one_sequence">Project 1</string>
    <string name="java_one_details">
        Suggested App Ideas
Details about a small business in your neighborhood
Contact info and description about your workplace or school
Info about a special interest group (like a club or sports team) you\’re part of and how new members can sign up
Requirements
Your design must include:

Business name
At least one photo representing the business
Two or more other pieces of information, such as:
Contact information for the business (eg phone number, email address, website)
Address of the Business
Description of business
Hours of operation
Note: This is not required but If you\’re up for a making real impact in your community, go check out an actual local business and obtain their consent to build an app for them!

Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="java_one_location">Project 1</string>

    <string name="java_two_name">Scorekeeper</string>
    <string name="java_two_category">User Input</string>
    <string name="java_two_sequence">Project 2</string>
    <string name="java_two_description">This project is a chance for you to combine and practice everything you learned in this section of the Nanodegree program. You will be making an app that allows a user to keep track of points within a game.
create an Score Keeper app which gives a user the ability to keep track of the score of two different teams playing a game of your choice. To build this project, you can follow along with the practice set and customize the Court Counter app to track scores from a different sport.</string>
    <string name="java_two_details">
        Why this project?
In the most recent portion of the Nanodegree program, you learned how to make use of Java in your Android apps to make them interactive. With Score Keeper, you will be practicing this skill set, with particular focus on button code, variable scope, and updating views.

What will I learn?
This project is about combining various ideas and skills we\’ve been practicing throughout the course. They include:

Adding button code to your app
Updating views
Properly scoping variables
Finding views by their ID
Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.

    </string>
    <string name="java_two_location">Project 2</string>

    <string name="java_three_name">Chess Openings Quiz</string>
    <string name="java_three_category">User Input</string>
    <string name="java_three_sequence">Project 3</string>
    <string name="java_three_details">
Why this project?
So far in this Nanodegree program, we\’ve built three apps together: the Happy Birthday, Court Counter and Just Java apps. At this point, we believe that you\’re now ready to create your own app. You will have full ownership over the creative vision, planning, and development of the app. From what we\’ve seen in the discussion forums, you each have a wealth of different experiences and unique areas of expertise. We would like to see that shine through in the app that you create.

What will I learn?
This project is about combining various ideas and skills we\’ve been practicing throughout the course. They include:

Planning your app design before coding.
Taking an app layout from drawing to XML code.
Creating, positioning, and styling views.
Creating interactivity through button clicks and Java code.
Commenting and documenting your code.
Paid Nanodegree Program vs Free Course
If you are in the paid Nanodegree program, you will receive feedback after submitting your project.

If you are enrolled in the free version of this course, the project rubric and all of the project details are available to you but you will not be able to submit nor receive feedback on your work.

Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="java_three_description">The Quiz App project is a chance for you to combine and practice everything you learned in this section of the Nanodegree program. You will be making your own Android app - taking it from the idea stage to building out the full app. You can share your app with family and friends, as well as with other students in this course.

The goal is to create an educational app that quizzes a user about a certain topic of your choice. We want you to be creative about how you accomplish this. It\’s up to you what the quiz questions will be about and how you want to present them to your user. (Per the rubric, we require a minimum of 4 questions and a maximum of 10 quiz questions for a proper app submission).
</string>
    <string name="java_three_location">Project 3</string>

    <string name="java_four_name">Musical Structure</string>
    <string name="java_four_category">Multiple Screens</string>
    <string name="java_four_sequence">Project 4</string>
    <string name="java_four_description">This project is a chance for you to combine and practice everything you learned so far in this section of the Nanodegree program. You will be making the structure of a music app using Intents, New Activities, Arraylists, Loops and Custom Classes.

The goal is to design and layout the flow for the structure of a Music Player app. Note that for this project, the app does not actually need to play music.

There are many music player apps, and they employ a wide variety of design choices. It will be your job to decide on the kind of structure that you would like your music app to have and build that structure using intents. Will you build an app to play music from the user\’s library of music? Will you build an app to stream random songs from a database? Will you build a musical suggestion engine? Those choices are up to you!
</string>
    <string name="java_four_details">
      Why this project?
In the last portion of the Nanodegree program, you learned how to think about the structure of an app and how to use OnClickListeners and explicit Intents to link between different activities within your own app. You also learned how to loop through an ArrayList to retrieve and display information to a ListView. Practicing these skills will drastically improve the quality of the apps you build down the road.

What will I learn?
This project is about combining various ideas and skills we\’ve been practicing throughout the course. They include:

Designing an app experience to achieve a certain goal
Creating new activities
Using explicit Intents to link between activities in your app
Using OnClickListeners to add behavior to buttons using Java code.
Creating your own Custom Class
Looping through an ArrayList
Populating a ListView or GridView with an ArrayAdapter
Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="java_four_location">Project 4</string>

    <string name="java_five_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="java_five_description">The final project is a chance for you to combine and practice everything you learned in this section of the Nanodegree program. You will be making your own multi-screen Android app to share your knowledge about a city you are very familiar with.

The goal is to create a Tour Guide App which presents relevant information to a user who\’s visiting your city. The app can list top attractions, restaurants, public places, or events for the city. It can contain all the best known secrets that only locals know. It’s up to you which categories you want to provide, as well as what information to provide in each category.
</string>
    <string name="java_five_category">Multiple Screens</string>
    <string name="java_five_sequence">Project 5</string>
    <string name="java_five_details">
Why this project?
In the most recent portion of the Nanodegree program, you worked to build the Miwok language app, which taught you how to present information in a multi-screen app to your users. Now, you will practice that skillset by presenting information that you care about in your own life to a user. Your Tour Guide app will be unique to your city, your life, and your interests.

What will I learn?
This project is about combining various ideas and skills we’ve been practicing throughout the course. They include:

Planning your app design and navigation before coding
Selecting proper data structures to store lists of information
Building layouts to display those lists of data
Navigating between lists in Fragments using either a ViewPager plus TabLayout or Navigation Drawer*
Creating your own custom classes
Properly handling images or audio (if applicable)
* Navigation Drawers were not covered in this course, but you may choose to implement it in this app.

Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="java_five_location">Project 5</string>

    <string name="java_six_name">News API</string>
    <string name="java_six_description">The final project is a chance for you to combine and practice everything you learned in this section of the Nanodegree program. You will be making your own app that connects to the Internet to provide news articles on a topic of your choice.

The goal is to create a News Feed app which gives a user regularly-updated news from the Internet related to a particular topic, person, or location. The presentation of the information as well as the topic is up to you.
</string>
    <string name="java_six_category">User Input</string>
    <string name="java_six_sequence">Project 6</string>
    <string name="java_six_details">
Why this project?
In the most recent portion of the Nanodegree program, you worked to build the News app. Along the way, you learned about connecting to the Internet in Android, parsing responses from an API, updating the information in your app, and properly displaying that information. Practicing these skills is imperative in order to build apps that delight and surprise users by anticipating their needs and supplying them with relevant information.

What will I learn?
This project is about combining various ideas and skills w\e’ve been practicing throughout the course. They include:

Connecting to an API
Parsing the JSON response
Handling error cases gracefully
Updating information regularly
Using an AsyncTask
Doing network operations independent of the Activity lifecycle
Use Uri.Builder class to add query parameters to the URL
Note: As the focus of this program is Java, only projects completed with Java as the source code will be accepted. Projects using Kotlin as the source code will not be accepted.
    </string>
    <string name="java_six_location">Project 6</string>

    <!--    Images' descriptions-->
    <string name="image_description">cape_image</string>
    <string name="image_background_description">Background for opaque image</string>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="phone_contact">Phone Contact</string>
    <string name="mail_contact">Email Contact</string>

    <!--    Drawings' Strings-->
    <string name="drawing_one_name">EmojiGram</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_details">A sketch manipulation of the Android logo surrounded by an
        ambigram of RogerVanWyk</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_description">Ambigram surrounding a droid</string>
    <string name="drawing_one_location">App Icon</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_name">Sketch 2</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_details">Sketch 2 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_description">Sketch 2 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_two_location">Sketch 2 location</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_name">Sketch 3</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_details">Sketch 3 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_description">Sketch 3 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_three_location">Sketch 3 location</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_name">Sketch 4</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_details">Sketch 4 details</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_description">Sketch 4 description</string>
    <string name="drawing_four_location">Sketch 4 location</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Welcome to my Android Portfolio.\n\nClicking on a project will display its details\n\nLong clicking a project will open the selected app for testing.</string>
    <string name="action_intro">Introduction</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="action_cv">CV</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="notes">NOTES</string>
    <string name="abnd">ABND</string>

</resources>